♪ ♪
Good party, huh?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, they always
seem to have a good time.
Two olives here.
Okay, there you go.
See you in a minute.
He's over there down the hall.
Oh, I see him, thanks.
Hi. Hi.
Well, you did it again, Cal.
You expected otherwise?
Darling, she looks absolutely
gorgeous in that color.
Darling! Hi.
Oh. Vodka martini,
dry, two olives.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Well, if I had all of this,
I'd be willing to
admit I was 40.
I'm going to go check
on the champagne.
Excuse me.
Sweetie, all I can say is
I wish I'd seen him first.
Thank God I did.
You know after Rick died, I
never thought that I could...
But these past three
years have been wonderful.
I have never seen you happier.
Mom also looks the best ever.
Tony Morgen, you are smooth.
Now, this handsome boy
should be out enjoying himself.
- Who says I'm not?
- Amazing.
Well, you know me,
always comfortable.
Those things'll kill you.
You wish.
Party's going well, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah.
Mom's money makes
everything go well.
I thought we had
an agreement, Tony?
No arguments tonight.
Nothing to spoil your
mom's party, okay?
What, me?
Nah, I wouldn't do
anything like that.
You really think you
got it made, don't you?
Just walking around here
like you own the place.
You don't.
My mother does.
And you're just using her.
Let's get something straight
right now, Tony, okay?
I love your mother.
For her money.
And I wouldn't do
anything to hurt her,
which is why I have not told
her what I know about you.
Oh, and what is that, Cal?
I was wondering
where you two were.
Mom, hey! I was just
coming to find you.
I thought maybe we'd
have a little dance.
Oh, great.
Excuse me, Tony.
Bonnie,
I believe that's our song.
Next dance, sweetheart?
Yeah, sure.
Shall we?
Oh, that was the nicest birthday
I ever had, Cal, thank you.
My pleasure, love.
Tell Tony the rental
company is coming
to pick up the tables
and chairs at noon today.
Tony was going to go to the
club for a swimming workout.
Can't he go later?
Oh, I'd rather not ask him.
I'll ask him.
You'll order him.
And then he'll get
mad and you'll argue.
And he'll twist you
around his little finger.
He loves me.
When his father died, he
took care of everything, of me.
He needs discipline.
Honey, I want you to
reconsider military school.
No.
Absolutely not. You must.
For our sake.
For our sake, Bonnie.
Don't you see it's
happening again?
We argue about
only one thing... Tony.
Always Tony.
Don't you see, Bonnie,
he's tearing us apart?
I love you and I
think you love me.
I do. I want us
to be happy, Cal.
I'll think about it.
Good.
I gotta go. Okay.
Mom! I thought you'd left.
No, Cal did, but I'm waiting
for the rental company.
Could've asked me.
Well, Cal and I knew you
wanted to go swimming.
I wouldn't have minded.
I really am trying, you know.
I know you are,
sweetheart, and I'm
sorry it's been so difficult.
It's just you're here
and Cal's there...
and I'm caught in the middle.
Look, about this
family counseling.
You said you wouldn't go.
Well, I know, but
I've been thinking
and I just want
everything to be okay.
And maybe if Cal and I
spent more time together,
things would work out.
Thank you, sweetie. Thanks.
Hi. Hi.
How are you?
This is a surprise.
We need to talk.
Sure.
Okay, just in there?
Sure, you bet.
I'm sorry about this morning.
Tony says that he's
ready for family counseling.
Yeah? Yeah.
Uh, well, uh, Tony
has said that before.
And if you remember, we went.
He never bothered to show up.
I know, but this time, he
says that he wants to go.
He needs to know
that we trust him.
I don't anymore.
So what, we just
make him disappear?
We just ship him off
to school, is that it?
If you want to save
this marriage, and I do.
We've been through
this so many times before.
When is it going to be resolved?
Bonnie, listen to me.
Our relationship can't last
with the three of us
in the same household.
Open your eyes.
It's more than a
personality conflict.
Tony lies.
Tony cheats. How dare you!
Tony's my son.
I'm not going to send him away.
You can't handle that...
then you can leave.
That's no solution.
I'll do whatever I have
to, to protect Tony.
Even from you.
Mr. Ritter, I'm
sorry Mrs. Ritter.
It's 5:00
and my ride's here. I
just wanted to let you
know I was leaving.
I'll see you.
Here she is, Mr. Morgen,
all washed and dry.
Thanks.
You have a good day, sir.
Uh, Mario. Hey. Yes, sir?
Thank you, sir.
You drive carefully.
I'm sorry to call you
so late in the day,
but I need to cancel our
meeting tomorrow morning.
I hope this isn't too much
of an inconvenience for you,
but I've got a big deal
going with some clients
from the West Coast... Hello?
Hold on. I'm here.
Hello?
Hi, Cal, it's Dan.
Yeah, hi, Dan.
How're you doing?
I've got to reschedule.
Is Wednesday okay? Uh-huh.
No, no, Wednesday will be fine.
I've got to go out of town.
Yeah, have a great trip.
Thanks. See you then. Bye-bye.
Hi.
Thought I'd drop by.
Table looks good.
What is that? Uh...
Is that oak?
Very nice. I like that.
I like the feel of wood.
Good.
You've got a lot of
nice things here, Cal.
I should probably
visit you more often.
I think it would be interesting
to learn about your business.
Maybe we could work out
some kind of a
part-time kind of thing?
Of course, I'd, I'd have to
commute from military school,
so I-I probably couldn't,
couldn't come every day.
You're not sending
me to military school.
Oh, yes, I am.
No, no, I'm not going anywhere.
Well, you don't have
any choice in the matter,
Tony.
Either you go voluntarily,
or I tell your mother
what I know. Yeah,
and what is that, Cal?
For one thing, I should
never have fired Shirley.
You stole this,
didn't you, Tony?
And you stole everything else
that I accused
Shirley of stealing.
What did you, uh,
tell Mom about that?
Well, I told her I misplaced
it and I just found it again.
But if you push me,
I'll tell her that you stole it.
The point is, Tony,
pawn shop records
have your name on them.
And there is nothing that
you can do to change that.
Case closed.
You're wrong, Cal.
♪ ♪
Yes?
Are you Mrs. Calvin Ritter? Yes.
I'm Lieutenant Bob
Brooks, Atlanta Police.
There's been a fire at
your husband's studio.
Oh, my God.
Is Cal okay?
I'm sorry.
Fire spread fast.
Your husband was dead
when we got there.
Oh, Cal.
Cal.
Tony.
Tony!
Mom, what's going on?
What happened?
It's Cal.
He's dead.
How?
There was a fire in his studio.
Lots of flammable
material around.
He was always so careful.
Yes, ma'am, I'm...
I'm sure he was.
We have a reason to suspect
arson and a possible homicide.
I'm, uh, sorry, Mrs. Ritter.
Uh, I know this is
not the best time,
but I'm going to have to ask you
to accompany us
downtown to the station.
Now?! I'm sorry,
but there's lots of questions
that need answering.
All right, let me go
with you. No, no, no, no.
You should stay.
Stay here and...
and call... call Evie,
and I'll... I'll take care of...
things. All right. Okay.
All right.
I'll take care of everything.
I promise.
Ben, I don't understand
what's going on.
Why am I here?
They think that Cal was killed.
Bonnie, they think it was you.
Me? Why?
What time did you leave Cal?
Uh... I don't... I don't know.
Um... ten after 5:00?
Couldn't have been
earlier than that?
No. Um, the guard came in
to say he was going,
and that was at 5:00.
And I-I left a few
minutes after that.
The clocks in Cal's
studio stopped at 5:15.
According to the fire marshal,
that means you were
there when the fire started.
I'm, uh, sorry to
have to do this,
but in light of the evidence...
Your presence at the scene
moments prior to the crime,
your lack of an alibi
at the estimated
time of the fire
and eyewitness testimony...
I'm sorry, I have no choice
but to place you under arrest
for the charge of
murder in the first degree.
Oh.
Arson, huh?
No faulty wiring.
Everything seemed
to be in order.
Yo, Ben.
Hi, Bob.
Glad I caught you.
What's up?
Well...
it's real embarrassing.
Uh... boys down at the station
were cataloging items
that we took from the scene
of the crime.
There was a tape and a
phone answering machine.
We played it down,
and there it was.
Cal Ritter must have picked up
in the middle of his message
'cause his voice is there
answering a call at 5:25,
which means someone
set back the clocks.
Well, if my client's got
an alibi for that time,
you might as well
start dropping charges.
Yeah.
You know, uh,
wouldn't hurt to...
wash your car once a year.
I did.
March 31.
Huh.
Hey.
There's a lot of
that going around.
Damn.
Now, let's see.
The electricity went
off at, uh... uh, 5:15,
and-and that's when the police
thought the murder took place,
but Cal answered a call at 5:25,
so all we have to know
is where you were at 5:25.
In the car.
Well, did you make a
call or stop at the house?
Uh-uh.
Got gas?
No.
Groceries, ice cream cone?
No, I-I just drove around.
I needed to think.
I'm sorry. I didn't go anywhere.
I didn't talk to anyone.
Well, the police will
only have your word
that you actually left
Cal's shop at 5:10.
I'm sorry.
I know you are.
I am, too.
It was worth a shot.
Ice tea?
Uh, Miss Malone, here let me...
Oh, thank you. Let
me help you with that.
It's very heavy.
Oh, it is, isn't it?
Thank you.
Where's-Where's the maid?
Oh, Cal, uh, fired her about
two weeks ago for stealing.
Can you imagine,
after eight years?
Shirley was stealing?
Well, Cal wouldn't
have fired her otherwise.
I mean, he was the nicest man.
Huh.
You know, I just don't know
what she's gonna do without him.
Huh.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
Hmm. Here.
Hi, everybody. Oh, hi, Tony.
Hi, Mr. Matlock.
Nice to see you again.
Nice to see you.
Uh, Miss Thomas?
Hi. I'm Tony Morgan. Oh.
I just want to thank you for
all you're doing for my mother.
Sure. How are you, Mom?
Hi.
It had to be a robbery, Ben.
It's the only thing
that makes sense.
Well, there was no
sign of forced entry.
Did Cal seem worried
or nervous lately?
No, no. He was in a great mood.
He threw a huge party for Mom
here at the house on Saturday.
No.
Uh, listen, Mr. Matlock,
uh, I don't want
to sound rude or anything,
but, uh, my mom's exhausted,
and she's been through a lot.
And I'm wondering
if we can maybe
just do this another
day, another time.
Oh, oh, certainly,
certainly, certainly.
Bonnie, we'll, uh...
we'll see you later on. Okay.
I don't know, Ben.
I don't, either.
Cal Ritter didn't
have any enemies.
He had one.
Shirley?!
Mr. Matlock.
How are you?
Just fine.
Uh, I guess you haven't heard.
I'm defending Bonnie Ritter.
I heard. Poor thing.
Maybe you could help
me with something.
I'm late for work.
Get in. I'll give you a lift.
Thank you.
So, you worked for, uh,
Mrs. Ritter for how long?
Would have been
eight years next month.
Oh, a member of the family.
My family's at home.
Mr. Matlock. Hi.
How you doing? Okay.
My mom's not here.
I know.
Go ahead with what you're doing.
Yeah, I was, I was
just helping my mother
go through Cal's papers.
You know, he
wasn't very organized.
Oh, that's a big responsibility.
Yeah.
Uh, when my father
died, I was only 13.
Um, but Mom and I did just fine.
It must've been very difficult
for you when she remarried.
I was happy for
her, Mr. Matlock.
I mean, uh... Cal
was a great guy.
And, uh, he made Mom happy
and that's really
all that matters.
Yeah. So you and
Cal got along okay?
Oh, yeah.
I mean, we
understood each other.
You never, you
never fought with Cal
or spied on him and your mother?
"Spied"?
Where... where did
you get that from?
From your housekeeper... former.
Shirley Taylor.
I'll tell ya, had Mom and
me completely fooled.
As a matter of fact, it
took Cal to figure her out.
You know what a
kleptomaniac is, Mr. Matlock?
Yeah.
I used to know a fella
that pronounced that
word "kleptominerac."
So, uh, Shirley was
a compulsive thief?
Yeah. I know.
I mean, she seemed
like such a nice person.
But, um, Cal mentioned
that her lying and her stealing
was just a sickness, so... Ah.
Did you go to her home?
Uh, no. No, I was,
uh, on my way there
and I saw her walking along
the, the street going to work.
So I picked her up
and gave her a lift... car.
So, anyway, tell your
mother I stopped by.
Okay, well, let me
walk you out. Okay.
Boy!
That's a beautiful car.
The man had good taste.
Yeah, he did.
Cal loved this car.
Um, I just, uh, I
can't remember.
Uh, the day Cal died,
uh, where were you?
At the club.
And you left about, um...?
Little after 5:00.
So that would, that'd put you home, what?
- 30.
Yeah. Uh-huh.
Was anybody in
the house but you?
No, I was alone.
Oh.
Huh? You better have
your car washed, Tony.
That could cause
trouble later on.
You know, every time I saw
Cal, he was wearing this jacket.
I had to talk Cal
into buying it.
He said it was too expensive.
Sometimes people that
are born and raised poor,
they have trouble spending
money on themselves.
I told him he deserved it.
Where's the lighter?
"The lighter"? Yeah.
Was it valuable?
Antique, 18 karat gold.
It had the initial "B"
in diamonds on it.
Ben, I'm telling you,
somebody broke in there,
and they robbed Cal
and they killed him.
Well, there's the
remains of Cal's watch.
That's an odd business that
somebody would take that lighter
and leave this expensive
gold watch behind.
When I think of some
of the things I said,
I'll never stop being sorry.
Good afternoon, ma'am. Hi.
Oh, I'm not staying.
Actually, I need to talk
to whoever was
working around 5:00
on Sunday the 15th.
Oh, not me, that's for sure.
Sunday's I kick back.
Oh. That'd be Mario and Eric.
Okay, either one of
them around now?
Oh, they're due in an hour.
Hmm...
Well, I'll come back.
Thanks.
Have a good one. Thank you.
There was no
sign of forced entry.
And in your experience,
what does that mean?
Well, whoever entered
was known by the victim.
The fire started
sometime after 5:15.
And given the
answering machine tape,
probably about 5:30.
Thank you, Captain.
Mrs. Ritter was still
there when I left at 5:00.
She told Mr. Ritter
to pack up and leave.
I've never seen a woman so mad.
Thank you. No further questions.
Cross-examine?
No questions at this
time, Your Honor.
Due to the hour, this
court will stand in recess
until 9:00 a.m.
tomorrow morning.
Didn't expect all that.
Well, we didn't even start yet.
I'm not a bit worried, no.
Don't you be, okay?
Mm-hmm. What you
need is to go home
and get some rest. Right.
Thanks, Mr. Matlock. Yeah.
Oh, Michelle?
You think you could
see, uh, Bonnie, home?
There are a couple
things maybe Tony could
help me out with. Fine.
Okay with you?
Yeah, sure. Okay.
Now, remember.
I do the worrying.
Reassure her.
Well...
Well, uh, I'll be
honest with you,
it's not really going very well.
No?
No, uh... I mean, I appreciate
you not wanting Mom to worry,
but you have absolutely nothing
to prove her innocence.
Well, that, that may be true.
And it's interesting
that you think that.
I'm not saying that
the D.A. isn't, uh,
doing the best she can.
And she does have a
few credible witnesses.
B-But look at all the
things she doesn't have.
There's no, no blood stains,
no fingerprints.
There's no physical evidence.
There's not one thing
to directly connect
your mother with
the fire or the murder.
That's a big problem. Hmm.
Juries like things obvious.
So you think Mom will get off?
Oh, yeah, she didn't kill Cal.
That's great. Yeah.
All right, see you tomorrow.
Okay.
Hey, Tony?
Tony?
Let, let me...
Uh...
Uh, see, it's not that
nobody cares who killed Cal.
As soon as your
mother's acquitted,
the police will reopen
this investigation.
And there's one thing
about Lieutenant Brooks.
He does not give up.
Okay. Great. Okay?
Bye. All right.
Excuse me.
Oh, hey, Tony! Tony! Yeah?
Uh, I have something to ask you.
Uh, I just... uh,
don't remember.
Um, the day Cal died,
what time did you
say you got home?
Uh, 5:30.
Uh-huh.
Could it have been, uh,
you know, five minutes earlier
or five minutes later?
Uh, yes, yeah.
Uh... No.
It's interesting
how casual people
are, uh, about time.
A person will tell you
that he'll meet you at, uh,
8:00, and he shows up at 8:15.
You know that? Yeah, yeah.
As if, uh, you know, a few
minutes on way or the other
doesn't make any difference.
But sometimes,
that can be important.
Like we all thought
the fire started around 5:00.
'Cause that's what the
killer wanted us to think.
How could he have known
that Cal would receive a
call on his answering machine
and answer it
personally at 5:25?
See?
So now, we believe
the fire started later.
And somebody
fiddled with the clocks.
So the killer, now,
has an alibi for
the supposed time,
but not for the real time.
Hmm. Yeah.
I didn't know that. Yeah.
That's interesting.
Yeah, well, I'll see you.
All right. Okay.
Uh, hey, Tony?
Tony, uh...
Sorry, just one other thing.
Uh, you remember this morning
when the guard was on the stand?
He said that, that Cal had, uh,
well, threatened
to send you away.
Yeah.
Well, clear something up for me.
Uh, I found a pile
of military school
brochures in Cal's office.
Well, there's
nothing to clear up.
It's just that, uh, you
know lots of families
send their kids away
to boarding school.
It's something that
Cal and I talked about.
Yeah, yeah, but here you are,
it's the middle of
your senior year
and almost all the
applications for college are in,
and it just doesn't make sense.
It didn't happen, so,
I mean, you know,
you don't have
to think about it.
Yeah, but... I mean, I do.
I think about a lot of things.
All right. Okay.
Listen, tell your
mother I'll be by
a little after 6:00. Okay.
If you need any help, I'll
be with you in a minute.
Uh, no, I'll...
I'll know what I'm
looking for when I find it.
Thanks, sir.
♪ ♪
Is that Tony?
Tony?
Mr. Matlock.
Miss Thomas, hi.
What are you doing?
Uh, nothing. Just, uh...
Are you burying something?
No, no! I was just, uh,
planting some
roses for my mother.
You know, I promised her that
I'd do it and, uh,
but I felt bad that I...
hadn't done it.
That...
looks like the sweater
your mother was wearing
the day Cal died.
No, no, I think you're
mistaken. Yeah, it does.
She was wearing it
at the police station.
There's, there's
something on there.
Give me that.
No, no-no. This...
we have to keep this.
This is evidence. Yeah.
Please, can't we just
make like it doesn't exist?
I wish we could,
Tony, but we can't.
See, I was trying
to help my mother.
And, and now, I've really just
gone and made it worse, huh?
Uh... looks like.
What are you looking for, Ben?
Same thing Tony was looking for.
Yeah...
How will you know
when you find it?
I don't know.
Well, there it is.
What? See?
No, what?
Nothing.
Mr. Matlock?
Call your next witness.
Uh, yes, sir, Your Honor.
Bonnie, we've been
friends for years
and I would never do
anything to hurt you, but...
I have to go ahead with this.
I'm sorry. Oh, Ben.
I call Tony Morgen to the stand.
Now, you have told the police
that on the day your
stepfather was killed
uh, after your swimming
practice, you went home.
Are you sure
you didn't go someplace else?
Positive. I went straight home.
You didn't go by your
stepfather's studio?
Uh, I said I went straight home.
Okay.
Okay, the reason, uh, I asked
was the day after your
step-dad was killed,
I drove over to his studio.
And, uh, the street
in front of the studio
has been resurfaced.
And, uh, my car got
tar splattered on it.
Same thing happened
to Lieutenant Brooks.
And when I saw that tar
had been splattered on your car,
I knew you had been there, too.
So when were you at your
stepfather's studio, Tony?
Um, sometime that week.
I don't know. I don't remember.
Maybe I can narrow
it down for you.
Uh, according to one of
the parking attendants,
uh, Mario Ruiz,
he remembers washing
your car that Sunday.
And the next morning,
you were driving your
stepfather's Porsche.
So that means, the only time
you could've gotten tar
splattered on your car
would be between the
time you left your club
and the next morning
when you were driving
your stepfather's car.
Well, uh, Mario was mistaken,
because he didn't wash
my car that Sunday.
Oh, no, Mario wasn't mistaken.
For a very good reason.
He gave him a five spot.
You tipped him five dollars.
Money means a
lot to you, doesn't it?
Having it, possessing it,
holding it, buying things
with it, showing it...
It makes you feel
important, doesn't it?
I don't see you, uh,
turning your nose up
at money there, Mr. Matlock.
No, no, I like money.
Money's pretty.
It's green, it's
got numbers on it.
Some of them go
way on up yonder.
But you have to
have a strong regard
for what money
can and cannot do.
The trick with money
is to enjoy it.
If you've got it, 'cause
a lot of people don't.
Lot of people.
But if you've got it, enjoy it.
Not need it to the point
that you cannot
stand the thought
of being without it. That's...
How would you
describe your relationship
with your stepfather?
We got along.
Even though your mother's life
was a constant struggle
to try to keep peace
between the two of you?
Uh, no. We were
a very happy family.
Why was he planning to
send you to military school?
He wasn't.
Uh, we, you know,
we had discussed it
and, uh...
he changed his mind
and decided it would
be best if I stayed home.
Oh, I see. I see.
I see.
Uh, your mother,
your mother had a, a housekeeper
named, uh, Shirley
Taylor, didn't she?
Yes. Yeah.
What happened to Miss Taylor?
Uh, Cal fired her for stealing.
Oh. And among the
alleged items that she stole
was an antique gold
lighter, isn't that right?
Maybe, yeah. She
stole a lot of stuff.
B-But you are very familiar
with that antique gold lighter,
aren't you?
I, I don't know.
She was a thief
and I, I don't know.
Maybe she just pawned it, huh?
Could be.
What do you think it was worth?
Lighter, old like
that... I, I don't know.
You know exactly what
it's worth to the penny.
Because you stole it.
And you pawned it.
No, that's not true.
Yes, it is.
And then you framed Shirley
knowing that Cal would fire her.
And that gave you someone
to blame your thefts on.
And you had been stealing
from Cal for a very long time.
And you got rid of
the only other person,
besides the family, who
had heard the arguments
between you and your stepfather.
There were no arguments.
Shirley Taylor can
and will take the stand
and say that you and Cal Ritter,
your stepfather,
fought constantly.
And that you spied on
your mother and him,
and that he intended
to send you away.
My mother would not permit that.
I'm the man of the house.
Not after she
married Cal Ritter.
Cal Ritter was the
man of the house.
Cal Ritter took your
place in the house.
You were no longer
central to your mother's life.
Cal was now taking her time.
Cal was now
taking her attention.
She was buying
him fancy sports cars,
watches... all the things she
should have been buying you.
Things that were
important to you.
She loves you, but now she
had someone else to love.
And he loved her.
And he could take her
into their secret room
and close the door.
Close the door on you.
And what's more,
that same man was planning
to send you away...
Send you away from your home.
From your mother!
Your Honor...
may I speculate for a moment?
Madam D.A.?
I hate it when he does that.
He tells these stories
like he's spinning a web.
Now, where is the proof?
Proof. Proof.
All right, all right.
Your Honor? Go ahead.
Thank you.
That Sunday, when
you left the club...
you didn't go straight home.
You drove out to
your stepfather's studio
and there, the two of
you had a hell of a fight.
Maybe about the military school.
Maybe about the fact
that he had discovered
you were the one who
was stealing and not Shirley.
Maybe he threatened to tell your
mother what he knew about you.
But whatever it was,
you knew he had you cold.
So you picked up something.
Maybe a piece of wood.
And you hit him.
You hit him hard
and you killed him.
And then, to erase your tracks,
you set a fire.
Then, to give
yourself a good alibi,
you set all the clocks back.
And then, in a final
act of disregard,
you took that
antique gold lighter.
The one Cal had found
in a pawn shop where you
had pawned it.
I didn't kill Cal.
I didn't want to
believe you had.
And I wish you hadn't.
But when I saw you burying
your mother's sweater
that convinced me.
There are any number
of flammable materials
that you could've
poured on that sweater.
But you chose paint stripper.
Only the killer could've known
that paint stripper was
used to start that fire.
You tried to incriminate
your own mother.
You remember, uh...
you remember the day
I found you going through
Cal's papers on his desk?
I was helping my mother.
You were looking for
a credit card receipt
that would prove that Cal had
redeemed that antique lighter.
No, I wasn't. And you found it.
Probably burned it.
But you left the folder
with the rest of the bills.
And when I was going
through them later,
I found those
credit card receipts
and they were all there,
except for the month of July.
But the credit card company
was very cooperative.
And they gave me a copy.
And there it is.
July 18.
Cal bought that
antique lighter back
from the Walnut Street Pawn Shop
where you had
pawned it for $1,500.
So...
when Cal was killed,
he had the lighter.
You mother saw it in the studio.
Harry the guard saw it.
But after the fire,
it was not in his
personal effects.
It was not in the studio.
We searched...
200 pawn shops
till we found this lighter.
This is the antique
lighter, isn't it?
With the letter "B" in diamonds?
Only the killer
could've possessed
and pawned this lighter.
You couldn't stand
to leave it, could you?
You couldn't stand not
to steal it one more time.
Not when you could get $1,500.
Give it up, son.
The man from the pawn
shop in Jacksonville
can identify you.
You shouldn't have
married him, Mom.
He was going to send me away.
I had to do it.
You know, I had,
I had no choice.
You understand that.
Don't you?
I'm sorry.
www.tvsubtitles.net